We'll be right back.
Give Robin back!
Luffy vs. Bluno!
What are we going to do?
What the hell?
It's too late now.
Even if we wanted to, it's not like we could go back and pick him up.
I'm sure he'll figure out something or other.
But the whole island is swarming with marines.
He's not Luffy after all.
He can't fight them off on his own.
Even if we don't realize it at first, we've gotten stronger with every challenge we've faced.
You may not think he's tough, but he's survived as well as anyone else.
No one from our crew would die at a time like this.
Don't worry.
From our crew?
Huh?
What are you talking about, Zoro?
Sniper King may be here to help, but he doesn't replace Usopp.
You don't know if he's gonna be okay or not!
He'll be fine.
He is a superhero after all.
You're right!
Sniper King would never let evil triumph over good!
He can't lose!
Why'd I have to not land on that king bull?
What am I gonna do?
I'm way behind everyone else now!
Battleship Denny!
These shipwrights are awesome!
But I should probably catch up with the others.
Then again, I did leave the crew, didn't I?
Maybe I should just run away.
No!
Running is the last thing I should do!
It doesn't matter whether I'm a part of the crew or not!
I put on this disguise so I can help my friends!
If Robin is willing to sacrifice herself to save us, it's the least I can do!
My manhood's on the line here!
All right.
There's only one way to get back to the others at this point.
I call it Operation Disguise Myself as One of the Government Agents
and walk straight to the courthouse without anyone noticing.
Okay, let's do this!
Ah!
Enemy attack!
They're flooding the island!
We're all gonna sink!
Ah!
The giant woke up!
We tried for 50 years in Pruitts!
Ah!
We let up on the cows!
You mean the government?
Ah!
We're distressed all the giants in Elbath!
I'm Sniper King from Sniper Island!
I'm interested in your story, by all means, continue!
Never heard of you and never heard of Sniper Island either!
I don't gotta tell you anything, okay?
Okay!
Calm down!
The warriors from Elbath are the proudest men in the world, right?
I know you wouldn't be crying if it wasn't a really big deal!
So tell me, what's going on?
I won't judge, I promise!
Hey...
Take your time.
There's not much point in telling you, but I guess it can't hurt.
Ah!
Hmm...
Kashi and I used to be pirates a hundred years ago.
Our crew traveled the whole world.
Back then, no one could stop us.
Huh?
But everything changed when we visited a certain island.
Cheers!
It's not every day someone bags a huge sea king, and they each got one.
Now that's impressive.
Yeah, take us for example.
We're Elbath giants.
No greater warrior exists.
But even we don't come close to taking down one of those massive beasts.
Wouldn't you say that's there, man?
Yeah!
I bet no one's ever slain a bigger sea king than us.
A conquest destined to become legend.
Awesome! So which one was bigger?
Hmm, which one?
Look at them side by side, Froggy.
Mine is slightly bigger, see?
Keep dreaming. Mine beats yours by three whole centimeters.
What? You're joking!
You wish!
Bosses, please!
Stop bickering!
Since they couldn't come to an agreement,
our two bosses started a duel.
They put their pride on the line
and would keep fighting till it was settled.
Who were we to stop them?
The signal for the duel.
We had to split up the crew.
We were at a loss.
All we could do was go back to our hometowns.
He's gotta be talking about Little Garden.
What else could it be?
A warrior's battle is life or death.
But as soon as it's over,
the winner is supposed to come back to their village.
We waited for 50 years and never heard from either of them.
Something was wrong.
So Kashi and I set out to sea to go back to the island and find out what happened with the duel.
But on our way there,
we got captured by some Marines.
They forced us to answer all kinds of questions about our crew.
Then we found out the truth.
Even though our bosses were strong fighters,
they got caught by Marines just like us
and were stuck in some big government jail.
Huh?
All of that stuff happened about 50 years ago.
Ugh.
The government made a deal with us.
They said if we would work for them for 100 years,
they'd set our bosses free.
All we had to do was protect this gate from intruders.
As long as we didn't let anyone through,
when our time was up,
our bosses and us could all go back to Elbaf together.
Since China's lived to be 300 or so,
we didn't think it was so bad.
So we agreed to the deal and kept all of the bargain for 50 years.
But then those pirates came through the gate and ruined everything.
That's why I'm so ashamed.
That's why I'm crying.
It's not fair.
Now our bosses are going to be stuck in that dumb prison for the rest of their lives.
Hey, hold on.
Wait a second.
There's something funny about that story.
You think this is funny, you little jerk?
How dare you laugh at our pride?
I don't mean like funny ha-ha.
I mean funny weird.
Hey, what's so weird about it?
Before we came here, my crew met those bosses of yours.
And we saw them fighting their duel!
Their names are Dory and Bragi, right?
The warriors from Elbaf, fighting in an evenly matched duel.
Over and over again, for a hundred years!
How... how do you know their names?
You must be lying.
If you need more proof than that, I can tell you anything you want!
And then...
You still don't believe me?
What do I have to tell you?
They're weapons, maybe?
How do they fight?
73,'466 duels!
I know everything about them!
73,466 duels!
We really met them!
We really met them! I swear it!
We met them!
Everyone of you fought like true warriors in order to protect the pride of our duel.
And because you are willing to do that no matter what enemy you may face.
We will never let them destroy your pride, friends.
You must go straight ahead! Have faith in what we say!
Let's meet again someday.
Absolutely!
Go straight! Go straight! Go straight!
That doesn't matter! We've already been eight straight, okay? Keep going!
Let's go!
Ah, kakaku!
We're quiet!
They've got the sea itself!
The strength of Hellbath is just too amazing!
Friends, take care!
I look to them as my teachers, my masters,
and I swore to myself that I would become
a great man of pride like them someday!
And you still don't believe me when I tell you this?!
They weren't captured 50 years ago!
That's nothing but a big fat lie!
Then our bosses are still out there?
They're still fighting there too?
I'm so glad!
They're still okay!
Even after all these years!
He he he he he!
He he he he he he he he!
Ha!
Look! We're almost to the courthouse!
This ought to stop him.
We've been hit! No!
Alright! We finally got one!
Sodom!
No! This is bad! He needs my help!
Sprint those teeth and hold on, Sodom! You can't fall yet!
Guys! You're gonna have to jump! Get off it quick!
Sodom can't go on!
That mortar hit him square in the chest! He's about to go down!
You gotta keep moving no matter what! You're the only ones who can do this!
He says go!
He's coming down!
No!
Nobody's riding it!
Where'd they go?
Come on, huh?
Let's go, Gamora!
So Robin is in that building behind you, huh?
Out of my way, bull guy!
Listen, boy.
Perhaps you haven't realized this.
But what you're doing right now is nothing short of a world-class crime.
Hmm?
We'll see you next time.